btcjam.com 2016-03-10

# BTCJam Privacy Policy - BTCJam

##  Privacy Policy 

Last Updated July 14, 2015 

This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) describes the collection, use and disclosure of information collected online by our website at www.btcjam.com (including any subpages or mobile versions thereof) or any other website where this policy is posted (“Site”). We are committed to maintaining the security and confidentiality of your personal and financial information. 

We also explain how any personal and/or personally identifiable information that the Company may request will be used; these explanations can usually be found on the same pages where the information is requested. Through your continued use of our Site, or by providing your Personal Information (as defined below) to us, you consent to the practices described in this Policy. 

###  Types of Information Collected by the Site 

The Company receives information from various sources: (1) when you register for Services with the Company; (2) when you use the Services; and (3) companies and individuals with whom we contract to perform business functions and services on our behalf including third party websites and services (e.g. data that you have expressly authorized the Company to use from your social networks such as Facebook and LinkedIn). 

In order to fulfill the Services of the Site we need to collect certain Personal Information and Financial Information to verify your identity and to assess your eligibility to borrow through the Company. Personal Information means any information that can be used to identify you as an individual. This includes the following: your full name; address; online contact information; government issued photo identification; telephone number; any persistent identifier that can be used to recognize you over time and across different services; identifiable location information; and third-party website log-in information; and Financial Information. Financial Information is information that you provide to us through the Site or any Application Protocol Interfaces (“APIs”) connecting to the Site. Any credentials you provide for access to financial institutions are passed on to one of our partners and are securely stored on their servers. For improved safety, we purposefully do not store any of your credit/debit card account credentials. 

If you provide explicit authorization for the Company to access data from a third party provider, such as Facebook, we will access and collect the personal information about you that the account provides based on your privacy settings with the third party provider. 

We also collect Personal Information about transaction and interactions with the Site such as IP address, browser, web beacons and similar technologies; or that your mobile device transmits when you interact with the Site. 

We also may also access public sources of information (e.g. national identity records or posts, pictures and other data you create and share on social networks). 

###  Use of Information by the Site 

Before or at the time of collecting Personal Information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected. We will collect and use Personal Information solely with the objective of fulfilling the Services and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law. We will only retain the Personal Information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of the Service. 

The Company will not share the personal information you submit to the Site, such as identity, and address unless you have borrowed a loan that is over 90 days in default and the loan is sent to the net-arb.com for arbitration. For more information on the arbitration process, click  [ here. ](http://www.net-arb.com/) If you are an investor in a loan that has been sent to arbitration, any information you have submitted to the Site will also be submitted to net-arb.com to assist you in collecting your investment. 

Borrower listings on the Site include certain non-Personal Information: your alias; reputation; your BTCjam rating; and any information you provide in the public area of the loan listing. Should you provide any Personal Information in a public area of the loan listing, the Company shall not have any legal obligation nor shall incur any liability for the sharing of the Personal Information. 

Beware of identity thieves who may try to trick you into giving them your personal or financial information. We never ask members to send personal information through email. If we ever require sensitive information, it will always be entered on the BTCJam site. We strongly encourage you to use two-factor authentication when using the Site. 

We do not sell or rent your information to third parties for marketing or any other purposes and we will protect Personal Information by using reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification. 

###  APIs 

Some of our features require us to access information hosted and provided by third parties. We may obtain access to the information provided by the APIs or other third party sites. We may, therefore, have access to Personal Information and/or sensitive Financial Information. We use this information to enable and execute features on the Site. 

By linking a third party provider to the Company via an API, you consent to the Company’s access to the information provided by that API and represent that you have the necessary authority to grant us access to this information. We strongly encourage that you use two-factor authentication if you allow the Site to access any Person and/or Financial Information through third party APIs. 

###  Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”) 

The Company complies with COPPA. This site is neither directed nor intended for minors under the age of 18. In the event that we have inadvertently collected Personal Information from a user under the age of 13, we will promptly delete it, in compliance with COPPA. Do not use this site if you are under the age of 18. 

###  Exclusions 

This Privacy Policy does not apply to any Personal Information collected by the Company other than Personal Information solicited and collected through the Site. This Privacy Policy shall not apply to any unsolicited information you provide to the Company through this Site or through any other means. This includes, but is not limited to, information posted to any public portion of the Site (e.g. comments on loan listings) or if you to choose to post comments on social network pages (e.g. Facebook or Twitter) and other unsolicited submissions (collectively, “Unsolicited Information”). All Unsolicited Information shall be deemed to be non-confidential and the Company shall not be held responsible for any of the subsequent use of the information whether it is by the Company or any third parties. 

The Company may disclose your Personal Information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) comply with a legal obligation; (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of the Company; (iii) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Site or the public, or (iv) protect against legal liability. 

###  Additional Agreements 

This Policy is incorporated into the terms of use applicable to each of our services and may include terms that are defined in those agreements. Any terms not defined in the Policy shall be defined by the BTCjam Terms of Use. Additionally, you may arrive at a third-party site or service when using the Site or a certain feature, in which case this Policy does not apply. Please see the terms and policies of those sites or services to learn how that party may collect, use and disclose your Personal Information. 

###  Limitation of Liability 

By providing us with any Personal information you expressly and unconditionally release and hold harmless the Company, its parents, subsidiaries, affiliates, related companies and their respective shareholders, owners, members, directors, officers, employees and agents (collectively, the “Releasees”) from any and all liability for any injuries, loss or damage of any kind arising from or in connection with the use and/or misuse of your collected Personal Information. In addition, while we take reasonable steps to prevent third-party companies from making unauthorized use of your personal information, we cannot be held liable for any injuries, loss or damage of any kind arising from or in connection with the use and/or misuse of your collected Personal Information by those third parties. 

###  Changes to the Policy 

This policy may change from time to time. We will post the most current version of this policy on the Site with the effective date. Your continued use of the Site means you consent to the terms of any new or updated privacy policy
